{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Home \u0026 Office Organizers","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40430/":{"taskOID":40430,"originalTaskOID":40430,"setID":721,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":4672,"questionDisplayText":"Reason for Consultant","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Why do you need a professional organizing consultant?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6410,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"To organize residence","answerDisplayText":"To organize residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6408,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"To organize family paperwork/bills/filing system","answerDisplayText":"To organize family paperwork/bills/filing system","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6400,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"To help balance work/home responsibilities","answerDisplayText":"To help balance work/home responsibilities","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6419,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"To run errands","answerDisplayText":"To run errands","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4893,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Prepare for garage/estate sale","answerDisplayText":"Prepare for garage/estate sale","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4897,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Prepare to move","answerDisplayText":"Prepare to move","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4898,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Prepare to sell home","answerDisplayText":"Prepare to sell home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6409,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"To organize in-home office for home business","answerDisplayText":"To organize in-home office for home business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4673,"questionDisplayText":"Areas to be Organized","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What areas need organizing?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3415,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Kitchen and cabinets","answerDisplayText":"Kitchen and cabinets","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1458,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Closets","answerDisplayText":"Closets","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2716,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Garage","answerDisplayText":"Garage","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":958,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Basement","answerDisplayText":"Basement","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6113,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Storage area","answerDisplayText":"Storage area","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3189,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"In-home office","answerDisplayText":"In-home office","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6955,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Whole house","answerDisplayText":"Whole house","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4675,"questionDisplayText":"Organization Problems","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kinds of things need organizing? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":1831,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Day-to-day clutter","answerDisplayText":"Day-to-day clutter","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2446,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Financial and other papers","answerDisplayText":"Financial and other papers","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2379,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Family photos, memorabilia","answerDisplayText":"Family photos, memorabilia","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5903,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Sorting assorted paper, mail, etc.","answerDisplayText":"Sorting assorted paper, mail, etc.","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4347,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Old belongings","answerDisplayText":"Old belongings","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":4672,"questionDisplayText":"Reason for Consultant","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Why do you need a professional organizing consultant?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6410,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"To organize residence","answerDisplayText":"To organize residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6408,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"To organize family paperwork/bills/filing system","answerDisplayText":"To organize family paperwork/bills/filing system","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6400,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"To help balance work/home responsibilities","answerDisplayText":"To help balance work/home responsibilities","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6419,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"To run errands","answerDisplayText":"To run errands","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4893,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Prepare for garage/estate sale","answerDisplayText":"Prepare for garage/estate sale","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4897,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Prepare to move","answerDisplayText":"Prepare to move","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4898,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Prepare to sell home","answerDisplayText":"Prepare to sell home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6409,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"To organize in-home office for home business","answerDisplayText":"To organize in-home office for home business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":6410,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"To organize residence","answerDisplayText":"To organize residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6408,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"To organize family paperwork/bills/filing system","answerDisplayText":"To organize family paperwork/bills/filing system","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6400,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"To help balance work/home responsibilities","answerDisplayText":"To help balance work/home responsibilities","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6419,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"To run errands","answerDisplayText":"To run errands","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4893,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Prepare for garage/estate sale","answerDisplayText":"Prepare for garage/estate sale","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4897,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Prepare to move","answerDisplayText":"Prepare to move","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4898,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Prepare to sell home","answerDisplayText":"Prepare to sell home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6409,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"To organize in-home office for home business","answerDisplayText":"To organize in-home office for home business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4673,"questionDisplayText":"Areas to be Organized","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What areas need organizing?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3415,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Kitchen and cabinets","answerDisplayText":"Kitchen and cabinets","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1458,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Closets","answerDisplayText":"Closets","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2716,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Garage","answerDisplayText":"Garage","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":958,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Basement","answerDisplayText":"Basement","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6113,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Storage area","answerDisplayText":"Storage area","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3189,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"In-home office","answerDisplayText":"In-home office","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6955,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Whole house","answerDisplayText":"Whole house","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":3415,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Kitchen and cabinets","answerDisplayText":"Kitchen and cabinets","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1458,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Closets","answerDisplayText":"Closets","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2716,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Garage","answerDisplayText":"Garage","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":958,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Basement","answerDisplayText":"Basement","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6113,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Storage area","answerDisplayText":"Storage area","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3189,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"In-home office","answerDisplayText":"In-home office","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6955,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Whole house","answerDisplayText":"Whole house","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4675,"questionDisplayText":"Organization Problems","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kinds of things need organizing? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":1831,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Day-to-day clutter","answerDisplayText":"Day-to-day clutter","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2446,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Financial and other papers","answerDisplayText":"Financial and other papers","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2379,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Family photos, memorabilia","answerDisplayText":"Family photos, memorabilia","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5903,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Sorting assorted paper, mail, etc.","answerDisplayText":"Sorting assorted paper, mail, etc.","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4347,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Old belongings","answerDisplayText":"Old belongings","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":1831,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Day-to-day clutter","answerDisplayText":"Day-to-day clutter","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2446,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Financial and other papers","answerDisplayText":"Financial and other papers","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2379,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Family photos, memorabilia","answerDisplayText":"Family photos, memorabilia","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5903,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Sorting assorted paper, mail, etc.","answerDisplayText":"Sorting assorted paper, mail, etc.","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4347,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Old belongings","answerDisplayText":"Old belongings","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/40430/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40430,"taskName":"Consultant - Professional Home or Office Organizer","taskDescription":"Find a Home Organizer Consultant","xmTaskDescriptor":"Home \u0026 Office Organizers","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":188,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Consultant Organizer Office organizing organize","textMessagingName":"Pro Organizer","rolloverLongDesc":"As consultants, these specialists help people organize everything from pots \u0026 pans to paperwork. Often employed after moves or in estate situations, these experts help people arrange their belongings in a systematic manner that reduces clutter \u0026 makes it easy to find things.","rolloverShortDesc":"Paperwork, space \u0026 time management \u0026 relocation help.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Find a Home Organizer Consultant.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Professional Home \u0026 Office Organizers \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":5,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":5,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Home or Office Organizing Consultant","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Consultant - Professional Home or Office Organizer","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Home Organizer Need","urlName":"Consultant-Professional-Home-or-Office-Organizer","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Home \u0026 Office Organizers - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Costs \u0026 Reviews","searchKeywords":"Consultant,Organizer,Office,organizing,organize,improvement","emcCategoryOid":-12052,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":721,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}